{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. When a cricket bat hits a cricket ball, impulse is applied on the_________",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Bat",
        "b": "Ball",
        "c": "Bat and Ball",
        "d": "No impulse is applied"
      },
      
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. Momentum is a ______ quantity",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Scalar",
        "b": "Vector",
        "c": "Infinite",
        "d": "Zero"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"3. The equation for impulse is_______",
      "answers":{
        "a": "F∆t=m∆v",
        "b": "F∆t=mu",
        "c": "F∆t=mT",
        "d": "F∆t=mRT"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"a",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"4. What is the SI unit of impulse?",
      "answers":{
        "a":"N/m",
        "b": "N/m2",
        "c": "N/s",
        "d": "kg/m"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"c",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. What is the SI unit of momentum?",
      "answers":{
        "a":"kgm/s",
        "b":"kgm/s2",
        "c":"kgm/s3",
        "d":"kg.m2"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"a",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"6. Change in momentum of an object is equal to the_______",
      "answers":{
        "a":"Internal Energy",
        "b":"Entropy",
        "c":"Impulse",
        "d": "Enthalpy"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"c",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"7. What is the unit of specific impulse?",
      "answers":{
        "a":"m/s",
        "b":"m2/s",
        "c":"m3/s",
        "d":"m/s2"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"a",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"8. What is the formula to find specific impulse?",
      "answers":{
        "a":"Jsp=m/v",
        "b":"Jsp= J/m",
        "c":"Jsp=T/m",
        "d":"Jsp=J/q"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"b",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
    },
    {
      "question":"9. Angular momentum is a _______ quantity",
      "answers":{
        "a":"Scalar",
        "b":"Vector",
        "c":"Infinite",
        "d":"Finite"
      },
      "correctAnswer":"b",
      "difficulty":"beginner"
      },{
        "question":"10. Angular momentum is proportional to __________",
        "answers":{
          "a":"Inertia and angular speed",
          "b":"Mass and angular speed",
          "c":"Angular speed and volume",
          "d":"Rate of change of angular speed"
          
        },
        "correctAnswer":"a",
        "difficulty":"beginner"
      }
  
  ]
}